Chris Angeloni

Philadelphia, PA Tel: (443) 615-6965

Email: chris.angeloni@gmail.com Website: www.chrisangeloni.com

Profile

PhD candidate in Psychology with 8+ years of experience in experimental design and analysis in academic settings. Experienced in designing experimental hardware and software and constructing data processing/analysis pipelines using a variety of data sources (human fMRI, EEG, eye-tracking and animal electrophysiology and behavior). Analytic techniques include parametric and non-parametric statistics, generalized linear models/regression models, and advanced machine learning. Presently seeking a Research Scientist position in a creative and forward-moving company.

Skills

Methods: electrophysiology, NIDAQ & Arduino programming, fMRI, EEG, machine learning, generalized linear models, signal processing and generation, experimental design and implementation in auditory neuroscience

Programming: MATLAB, Linux/Bash, Python, R, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Arduino, openGL

Experience

Graduate Student

University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA: August 2014 - present

- Designed and implemented electrophysiology experiments recording from mouse auditory cortex
- Developed new experimental rigs for acoustic stimulation and recording of electrophysiological and behavioral data
- Received multiple grant awards supporting research in neuroscience and supporting training in machine-learning and probabilistic modelling

OIST Computational Neuroscience Course

Okinawa Institute of Science and Technology, Okinawa, Japan: June 2018

- Selected from a limited applicant pool to attend this computational neuroscience training course
- Designed and implemented leaky-integrate-and-fire models of networks of neurons in Python

Research Analyst

University of Pennsylvania, Nashville, TN: June 2012 - June 2014

- Designed processing pipelines for functional magnetic resonance imaging data and eye-tracking data
- Aided in developing novel fMRI scanning protocols for ultra-fast scanning of small areas of tissue, as well as high resolution structural imaging using 7T scanners
- Developed independent research projects studying visual attention using eye-tracking, and spatial representations in the human hippocampus during virtual navigation

Education

PhD Candidate Psychology

Aug 2014 - present

University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA

GPA: 3.9

B.S. & B.A. Neuroscience & Studio Art

May 2012

Lafayette College, Easton, PA Magna cum laude - GPA: 3.9

Awards

Predoctoral Ruth L. Kirschstein National Research Service Award (NIDCD F31-DC016524) IGERT Traineeship in Complex Scene Perception (NSF 0966142) Rappolt '67 and Oeschle '57 Neuroscience Prize